(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS1)
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS2) iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS3)
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS4)
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS5)
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS6)
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS7)
(ADDRESS UNKNOWN PLAYS last)
♪ Address Unknown
♪ Not Even A Trace Of You
♪ Oh, What I'd Give
♪ To See The Face Of You
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
♪ I Was A Fool
♪ To Stay Away
♪ From You So Long
♪ I Should Have Known
♪ There'd Come A Day
When you'd be gone
♪ Address Unknown
♪ Oh, How Could I Be So Blind
♪ To Think That You
♪ Would Never Be Hard To Find?
♪ From The Place Of Your Birth
To the ends of the earth
♪ I've Searched Only To Find
♪ Only To Find
♪ Address Unknown
(KIDS GIGGLE)
(HUMMING)
MAN:  Address unknown.
Honey child,
I ain't even got
a trace of ya.
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
You know one thing?
I'd give anything in the world
just to see the face of ya.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I was a fool
to stay away from you
and everything else so long.
(GRINDING)
I should have been diplomatic
and figured that someday,
you'd be solid gone.
♪ Address Unknown
♪ Oh, How Could
I Be So Blind
(GRINDING STOPS)
♪ To Think That You
♪ Would Never Be Hard To Find?
♪ From The Place Of Your Birth
To the ends of the earth
♪ I've Searched Only To Find
♪ Only To Find
♪ Address Unknown ♪
WOMAN: (ON TV)  Yeah,
That is some detail.
That is some western detail
right there...
Western detail,
attention to detail.
Look, he's even got the spurs
on the back of his boots.
And they're sharp. They are.
CHRISTINE: (LAUGHS)  I love it.
WOMAN:  Well, the clock is gone
on this piece, Christine,
so...
(GASPS)  Oh, my goodness!
CHRISTINE:
Well, let's just move on.
CHRISTINE:  Well,
from time to time,
people make mistakes,
that's okay.
This is our first Renoir
of the evening.
This is a heliogravure,
which is an etching.
It was hand-pulled from a
copper plate in Paris in 1919.
We know this because that's
what it says on the back,
where the certificate
of authenticity is located.
Just as lovely as can be.
Look at the soft, delicate
shading, very feminine.
(SIGHS)
This is a limited edition.
This is what
you're looking for
if you are a Renoir fan.
WOMAN:
100, oh, my goodness.
Right at the buzzer.
CHRISTINE:  Whoo! Good.
MAN:  ...of the few
exceptions is the African
pancake tortoise,
which has a flat,
flexible shell
that allows it
to hide in rock crevasses.
Big swath
of light to moderate snow
from the broken bow
area down toward Kearney,
Hastings,
Grand Island, that is all
moving in our direction.
So I do think,
around 7:00 to 8:00,
the snow will become pretty
steady here across the region
with all this
moving on top of us,
and that's really gonna
knock down visibilities.
And, again,
snow-covered roads
are gonna be definitely
likely this evening,
making it even slippier,
or more...
(SIGHS)
More slippery than it is
out there at this time.
There's that winter-weather
advisory in effect
until very early
tomorrow morning.
We're gonna talk
snowfall totals
coming up after more news.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
REPORTER:
Will bitter, cold weather
help break up
the compaction issues
we created this fall
in our fields?
Well, we'll show
you where it will
and where it won't
during today's Iron Talk.
(CHAIR CREAKING)
When it comes to compaction...
(ICE CLINKING)
...There's really two
different types of compaction.
There's vertical compaction,
and there's
horizontal compaction.
And there's a big difference.
(CLATTERING)
With horizontal compaction,
there really isn't much hope
for help from a freeze thaw.
And the reason why, as that
hard, compacted layer swells
and then, in the spring,
thaws back out
and settles back down,
there's really no breaking up
of the compaction.
With a vertical zone,
when compaction swells out,
and then it breaks up
in the spring,
then you can actually
get a little bit of help.
So if you have some
horizontal compaction...
(VCR WHIRRING)
...Created
by doing some tillage
when it was a little too wet,
or...
(ICE CLINKING)
(BEEPING)
(THE BATTLE HYMN
OF THE REPUBLIC PLAYS)
SAUL:  Don't let false
allegations bully you
into an unfair fight.
Hi, I'm Saul Goodman,
and I will do
the fighting for you.
No charge is
too big for me.
When legal forces have you
cornered, better call Saul!
(BEEPING)
(JINGLE PLAYS)
I'll get your case
dismissed.
I'll give you
the defense
you deserve. Why?
Because I'm Saul Goodman,
attorney-at-law.
I investigate,
advocate, persuade,
and, most importantly, win!
(ECHOING)  Win... win... win!
Better call Saul.
(BEEPING)
(GOD BLESS AMERICA PLAYS)
Do you feel doomed?
Have opponents of freedom
wrongly intimidated you?
Maybe they told you
that you're in serious trouble
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
I'm Saul Goodman,
and I'm here to tell you
that they're wrong.
It's never too late
for justice. Better call...
(CLOCK TICKING)
(CHAIR CREAKS)
(MAN COUGHS)
(ICE RATTLES)
(SLURPING)
(MAN COUGHS)
(CHAIR CREAKS)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(MAN CLEARS THROAT)
(HINGES CREAKS)
JIMMY:  Think back...
Your brain...
It's just not all there yet.
Uh, if we were all
held responsible
when we were 19...
(CLAPS HANDS)
(CHUCKLES)
I remember what it was like
to be a kid. Think back.
(CHUCKLES) Tell 'em, Judge,
what would you say?
(DOOR CREAKS)
These boys, 19.
I can't, I don't,
these three young men...
(SIGHS)
Just like you.
Psst!
(SIGHING)
(DOORS CREAK)
(HINGES CREAK)
(CLAPS HANDS)
Oh, to be 19 again,
you with me,
ladies and gentlemen?
Do you remember 19?
Let me tell you,
the juices are flowing.
The red corpuscles
are corpuscling,
the grass is green,
and it's soft,
and summer's gonna
last forever.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Now, do you remember?
Yeah, you do.
(CLEARS THROAT)
But if you're being honest,
I mean, well,
really honest,
you'll recall that
you also had
an underdeveloped
19-year-old brain.
Me, personally, I, it,
if I were held accountable
for some of the stupid
decisions I made
when I was 19...
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, boy, wow.
And I bet if we were
in church right now,
I'd get a big "amen!"
Which brings us
to these three,
now, these three knuckleheads,
and I'm sorry, boys,
but that's what you are,
they did a dumb thing.
We're not denying that.
However, I would like you
to remember two salient facts.
Fact one,
nobody got hurt, not a soul.
Very important
to keep that in mind.
Fact two,
now, the prosecution
keeps bandying this term
"criminal trespass."
Mr. Spinowzo,
the property owner,
admitted to us that
he keeps most portions
of his business
open to the public
both day and night.
So, trespassing?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
That's a bit of a reach,
don't you think, Dave?
(CHUCKLES)
Here's what I know,
these three young men,
near honors students all,
were feeling their oats
one Saturday night,
and they just...
Went a little bananas.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't know.
Call me crazy,
but I don't think
they deserve to have
their bright futures ruined
by a momentary,
minute,
never-to-be-repeated
lapse of judgment.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you're bigger than that.
(MAN SNIFFS)
(WOMAN COUGHS)
(CHAIRS CREAKING)
(SNIFFS)
(WOMAN CLEARS THROAT)
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
(VCR WHIRRING)
(CLATTERING)
(LAUGHS)
BOY:
Kenny, Kenny, are you rolling?
Yeah, yeah. Wait a minute.
Yeah, baby, yeah!
BOY 1:  But, dude, but, dude,
pipe down.
Chill out, would you?
BOY 2:  Hey, Mrs. Watson's
fourth-period biology class,
this one's for you.
Watch and learn, losers.
Oh, yeah!
(LAUGHS)
(RHYTHMIC SQUISHING)
BOY1:  Oh!
BOY 1:  Oh, God!
BOY 2:  Dude! Where did
all the blood go?
KENNY:  Dude, he's dead.
They suck it all out, dumbass.
BOY 1: (LAUGHING)
Awesome. Where do they put it?
All right, I'm though
the neck bone now, dude.
BOY 1:  Oh, nice.
Kenny, get over here, man.
KENNY:  I'm, I'm getting it.
Get, get,
get this out of here.
BOY 1:  All right.
All right, fine.
Here, let me do it.
(LAUGHS)
KENNY:  I got it!
All right.
Oh, oh-oh!
Get that.
All right.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Here, let me do it.
Dude, get off!
BOY 2:  Chill out.
(LAUGHTER)
KENNY:  All right.
BOY 2:  Wait, wait.
BOY 1:  Oh. Oh.
Okay, wait for it. Wait.
Oh!
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah! Oh!
Whoo!
Come on!
Yeah, baby, yeah!
BOY 1:  This dude was,
dude, I dare you
to stick your wang
in the throat hole.
BOY 2:
I will if you will, loser.
KENNY:  Oh!
BOY 1:
All right, all right!
(LAUGHTER)
What the hell kind of math
is that?
WOMAN: $700 per defense.
No, no, no. "Defendant."
"...Dant."
Three defendants, $2,100,
which, by the way, bargain,
what I did for them.
They going to jail,
ain't they?
So, since when
does that matter?
They, they had sex
with a head!
Look, didn't nobody
tell you to try all
three of them together.
One trial, $700.
You're gonna miss me.
You are gonna miss me.
'Cause it'll be
a cold day in hell
before I do any more
PD work for this
shitty court!
Sayonara, baby!
You have yourself
a nice day.
(SCOFFS)
(BEEP)
(WAND WARBLES)
(SIGHING)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
(GROANS)
(HIGH-PITCHED BRITISH ACCENT)
Law offices of James McGill.
How may I direct your call?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yes, Mrs. Kettleman,
so good of you to return.
Actually, I don't have
Mr. McGill at the moment,
but I know he'd...
Oh, splendid.
Uh, unfortunately,
our offices are being painted
and the fumes
are quite horrid.
Um, uh, could he meet you
and your husband at, say,
uh, Loyola's Cafe
on Central?
4:00 it shall be.
Cheers.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(CAR DOOR CREAKS)
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(GEAR CLICKS)
(SNIFFS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
MIKE: $3.
(NORMAL VOICE)
Uh, I'm validated.
See the stickers?
Well, I see
five stickers.
You're one shy.
It's $3.
(SIGHS)
They gave me, look.
I'm validated
for the entire day, okay?
Five stickers, six stickers,
I don't know from stickers
because I was
in that court back there
saving people's lives,
so...
Well, gee,
that's swell.
And thank you
for restoring my faith
in the judicial system.
Now you either pay the $3,
or you go back inside
and you get
an additional sticker.
Son of a bitch.
(SCOFFS)
Fine. You win.
Hooray for you.
(SCOFFS)
Backing up!
I have to back up!
I need more stickers!
Don't have
enough stickers!
Thank you!
Thank you, very nice!
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
Employee of the month
over here!
Yeah!
(CLAPPING HANDS)
Hooray!
Give him a medal!
Don't do anything, guys.
Just relax, all right?
Well, I'm just fuzzy
as to why you think
he needs a lawyer.
I mean, Craig,
the way you run your office
is beyond reproach.
Yeah. Yeah.
Beyond reproach.
Yeah.
I'm a stickler,
you know, for...
He is.
He's a stickler
with the money.
He's definitely a stickler.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, he's certainly
not guilty of some...
Is certainly not.
He's innocent
of any wrongdoing.
That's abundantly
clear to me.
And frankly,
I don't go looking
for guilty people
to represent.
I mean... (CHUCKLING)
Who needs that aggravation,
right?
Right.
(LAUGHTER)
Look, all I know
is what I read in the paper.
And typically,
when money goes missing
from the county treasury,
and the number here is,
uh, $1.6 million...
Well, that's an accounting...
It's an
accounting discrepancy.
It's a discrepancy,
absolutely.
But typically,
when that happens,
the police
look at the treasurer.
And since that person is,
uh... (CHUCKLES)
I just think a little
proactivity may be in order.
Well...
You know, I just think I'd
look guilty
if I hired a lawyer.
Yeah.
No.
Actually, it's getting
arrested that makes
people look guilty,
even the innocent ones,
and innocent people
get arrested every day.
And they find themselves
in a little room
with a detective who acts
like he's their best friend.
"Talk to me," he says.
Uh, "Help me clear
this thing up.
"You don't need a lawyer,
only guilty people
need lawyers."
And boom!
Hey, that's when
it all goes south.
That's when you want someone
in your corner,
someone who will fight
tooth and nail.
(SIGHS) Lawyers, you know,
we're like health insurance.
You hope
you never need it.
But, man, oh, man,
not having it, no.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
How Would we proceed
if we decided to, uh...
Oh, well, this is a...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Letter of engagement.
It's very simple,
straightforward.
Please, uh, read it closely,
but if you sign it, um,
I can get started
on that defense
strategy of ours
this very afternoon.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CLICK ECHOES)
(DISTORTED CONVERSATIONS
IN DISTANCE)
(GULPS)
(THUD)
BETSY: Craig...
I think maybe
we should sleep on it.
Uh, sure.
Don't you think,
Mr. McGill?
Maybe we should
sleep on it.
Oh, oh, please,
call me Jimmy.
(CHUCKLES)
Absolutely.
I mean, there's no rush.
You...
Oh, and, you know, Craig,
we got to pick up the kids.
Oh. Right. Yeah.
BETSY: At the, yeah. Right.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, uh,
we will be in touch.
Oh.
Uh, thank you for the coffee
and for the advice.
You're very,
very welcome.
Oh!
(SNAPS FINGERS)
Um, here. Take this.
It's, uh, it's got
my phone number on it.
Yeah. Okay.
Got it.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SIGHING)
The number
is 9-4-5-6-
0-0-5-4-4-8-9-6-
0-6-4-3,
and the expiration is 11/04.
Okay, and the keyword here
is "classy," all right?
Super classy, use only flowers
that look expensive,
but, you know, aren't.
Uh, and the note
should say... (SIGHS)
"Dear Betsy and Craig..."
Uh, "Best wishes
from your stickler
for justice,
"James McGill."
Okay? And "McGill"
is spelled "M-C..."
Well, run it again.
Oh, no, no, no. It's paid up.
Run it again.
Oh!
(THUD)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(GASPING)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Oh...
LARS: Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
Oh.
Cal, Cal! Look at me!
Buddy, look at me.
Are you okay?
Say something.
What did you do?
I did...
What did you do
to my brother?
Why don't you look
where you're going?
I was making a turn!
He came out of nowhere!
You freaking,
freaking hit him, man!
I did...
You ran him over!
(COUGHING)
You ran over
my brother!
And I got the whole thing
on video.
It was an accident.
He didn't, he didn't mean to.
Let me just, aah! Aah! Oh!
No, no. That's broke.
That's broke.
You broke his leg.
It's my leg. Oh!
It's my leg. It's my leg.
Why are you driving around
and not looking?
Shh, shh, shh!
Driving around,
breaking people's legs!
It's, it's, it's, okay,
okay, okay!
Where's the,
somebody call the cops!
Don't call, don't call
the police.
Don't call the police.
Police!
CAL: Lars.
Policia!
Don't, don't, don't.
Don't call them.
I'll call them myself.
I'm doing it myself.
Don't call the police.
Don't call the cops?
No.
LARS: How you gonna
fix this?
What are you gonna do
to make things right?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I don't know, fellas.
(SIGHS)
What can I do
to make it right?
(SIGHS)
I don't know.
$500.
500 bucks?
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
Ow!
What the hell, man?
Listen,
Starlight Express,
I'm gonna give you
a 9.6 for technique,
0.0 for
choice of victim.
I'm a lawyer.
(LAUGHS)
Furthermore,
does, does this
steaming pile of crap
scream "payday" to you,
huh?
The only way that entire car
is worth 500 bucks
is if there's
a $300 hooker sitting in it.
Now, let's talk about
what you owe me
for the windshield.
You, what?
(GRUNTS)
(DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE)
I'll take a check!
(CONVERSATIONS IN VIETNAMESE)
(MAN SINGING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(BELL JINGLES)
(GREETING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(ALL SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
Mrs. Nguyen.
My, don't you look...
Got my mail?
You work for people
who have sex
with chopped-off head?
Was it in the paper?
I heard it from my cousin.
Why? Why you work
for these people?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Just lucky, I guess.
Cucumber water
for customer only!
(WASHING MACHINE RUMBLING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(LOCK TURNS)
(DOOR SCRAPING)
(KEYS JINGLE)
(SIGHING)
(SIGHS)
(DIAL TONE)
(RINGING)
FEMALE VOICE:
You have, zero messages.
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(SIGHS)
(ELEVATOR RUMBLING)
(TONES PLAY)
(ELEVATOR DOORS OPEN)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(TONES PLAY)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(TELEPHONES RINGING)
Oh.
Brenda, looking good.
Nice do.
Uh,
where's Lord Vader?
Uh, he's not quite ready
for you yet.
South conference room.
How about
you wait out here?
How about I don't?
(SCOFFS)
Oh, Sir Francis.
James.
Well-groomed,
as always.
Okay.
All right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Keith, Karen, yes.
(CLAPS HANDS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
You have meddled with
the primal forces of nature,
Mr. Hamlin,
and I won't have it!
BRENDA:  Do you want me
to call security?
It's okay, Brenda,
we got it.
(BUTTON CLICKS)
JIMMY: Hey, Jack.
Hey, Nate. Hey, Aaron.
What can we do for you,
Jimmy?
I'm sorry.
It's, it's this table.
Something just
comes over me.
You can tell me what this,
uh, $26,000
is supposed to be for.
That's money for Chuck.
Isn't that what you wanted?
A measly 26 grand?
(SCOFFS)
Jesus, you're like
Peter Minuit
with the Indians.
Throw in some
beads and shells
while you're at it.
It's just a start.
There'll be more,
unless you're gonna just
tear them all up.
And why was it
made out to me,
why not Chuck?
Can he make his way
to the bank?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
I just assumed
it was best
to have the money
go through you.
We can do it
any way you want.
This isn't going away,
Howard.
What Chuck
did for this firm,
and damn near
single-handedly,
1/3 of this place
belongs to him.
Yeah. What do you got,
12 chairs here?
Four of these chairs
are Chuck's.
You got five of these
light thingumajigs?
Uh, mmm,
1 2/3 are Chuck's.
Yeah. Six, how many
Danishes, six Danishes?
You can have all the
Danish you want, Jimmy.
No, no.
They're Chuck's Danishes,
and Chuck isn't greedy,
so he'll just
take two...
Plus $17 million,
in that ballpark.
I mean, we'll know
once we get the accountants
poking around here.
Until then,
no more penny-ante checks
designed to make it look
like Chuck still works here.
He doesn't.
He never will again.
It's time to do right by him
and cash him out.
So, these are
Chuck's own wishes
that you're conveying?
This is what's
best for him.
HOWARD: Mmm.
So he personally told you
that it's his wish
to withdraw
from the firm?
(SCOFFS)
See,
that would surprise me.
It's been nearly a year
since he's set foot in here.
I'm just doing
what's in his best interests.
So am I.
And I, for one, believe
he's gonna lick this thing.
Until then, his office
is just as he left it.
His secretary's
still on payroll.
If Chuck can call this
an extended sabbatical,
then so can we,
he's that important to us.
You know what?
Let's let a jury
figure it out.
(SIGHS)
Yeah, they're gonna
love you, Howard.
You're so down-to-earth
and relatable.
(FIRMLY)
And you will atone!
It's Ned Beatty,
from  Network.
For Christ's sakes, guys.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(TELEPHONES RINGING)
Jimmy.
I almost forgot,
this month's filings.
You could save me
the postage.
Weren't you listening
in there?
Chuck doesn't work here
anymore.
You think
I'm gonna help you
establish a paper trail?
Now, Jimmy...
No, stop trying to
pawn that shit off on him.
Jimmy.
You know, Jimmy, sometimes,
in our line of work,
you can get so
caught up in the idea
of winning
that you forget
to listen to your heart.
Give Chuck my love,
would you?
(SCOFFS)
Oh, there you are.
Betsy, Craig.
CRAIG: Ah.
BETSY: Hi. Okay.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(LAUGHTER)
(CONVERSATION CONTINUES)
You look
lovely today.
Oh, thank you so much.
(CONVERSATION CONTINUES)
(TONES PLAYS)
(SIGHS)
Couldn't you just...
You know, I can't.
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(GEAR CLICKS)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(TYPEWRITER KEYS CLACKING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLATTERING)
Aah! Son of a bitch!
CHUCK:
Ground yourself?
JIMMY: Yes,
I grounded myself.
(CLACKING CONTINUES)
(BELL DINGS)
(CARRIAGE SLIDES)
(CLACKING CONTINUES)
(GAS HISSES)
(SIGHS)
(CLACKING CONTINUES)
(ICE CLATTERING)
(BELL DINGS)
(CARRIAGE SLIDES)
(CLACKING CONTINUES)
You got to stop putting bacon
on the list,
'cause that cooler's
looking like
a trichinosis stew.
Perfect timing.
(CARRIAGE SLIDES)
Hmm.
(SIGHS)
"Professor
Brans Vogelson."
Mmm-hmm.
"University of Helsinki?"
Yeah, you're gonna have to
get that translated.
Into Swedish?
Finnish.
Finnish, uh,
translating into...
(SIGHS)
I'm sure there's someone
at UNM who can do that.
You do know
I'm trying to start
a legal practice, right?
Vogelson's been working
on the effects
of electromagnetic fields
on zebra fish, and, oh!
Financial Times.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Yeah, I knew you missed it,
so I figured, "What the heck?"
Thank you.
I know it's expensive.
Here.
(CLEARS THROAT)
That's not,
it's all right.
I don't expect you
to go out of pocket.
I...
Go ahead,
reimburse yourself.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Thanks.
Hey, Chuck, um,
can you not read
that for a second?
Can we talk?
Are you all right?
You look peaked.
I'm fine.
Please, just sit.
You're not in trouble.
Um...
You got to cash out.
You got to.
Again? Really?
There's no other way.
I know that
you don't want to hear it,
but you've got to.
You know
I'm going to beat this.
You know I'm going to
get better.
Yeah, sure.
(CHUCKLING) Well, then,
there's nothing more
to talk about.
I will beat this.
Ergo, a falsis
principiis proficisci.
Meaning?
That's not...
That's the one about false
principles, but it's not...
You proceed
from false principles.
Your argument
is built on quicksand.
Therefore, it collapses.
Yeah, yeah.
You're not listening.
(SIGHS) Fine.
Let's take this
to its logical conclusion.
(SIGHS)
In order
to pay out my share,
suppose my partners
are forced to
liquidate the firm.
Then what?
That's their problem.
My clients
are out in the cold.
My cases are scattered
to the winds.
126 people
lose their jobs.
What happens to
your cronies in the mailroom,
the assistants,
the paralegals,
the janitorial staff?
All of them,
out on the street.
Your friend Kim,
a promising career,
over and done with.
Hamlin
owes you everything.
You built that place
single-handedly
while he was out
at four hills working
on his bunker shot.
Let's not exaggerate.
I helped.
You helped.
(SCOFFS)
All the more reason
not to tear it down
just for a little bit
of cash.
Look, Chuck,
I'm going under, okay?
For the third time
with these bull-crap
contract counsel...
"Bull crap?"
Bull-crap, Pissant PD cases
at 700 bucks a shot.
Public-defender
work is some
of the best experience
there is.
(SIGHS)
I just had a case, Chuck,
with three clients,
uh, arraignments,
voir dire, jury trial,
the whole nine yards.
You know what I took home?
700 bucks.
Yeah, I might as well
head down to Skid Row
and sell plasma.
You're representing
people who have
nowhere else to turn.
The money
is beside the point.
Money is not
beside the point,
money is the point.
I keep telling you,
have patience.
There are no shortcuts.
Do good work,
and the clients will come.
The clients will come.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
Hand to God,
I wasn't gonna say this,
but you are broke.
I can't carry
both of us.
I've been trying like hell,
but I can't.
(CHUCKLING)
Well, you're saying what?
You think you have
to provide for me?
I never asked you that.
You didn't have to ask,
okay?
I've been doing
my damnedest,
but the day of reckoning
is here.
Soon, Chuck, you're gonna be
out on the street
with all the electromagnetism
in the world raining down
on you.
Now, please, please,
picture that,
then tell me that money
is beside the point.
This is what has you
all worked up?
Yeah!
Jimmy, there's nothing
to worry about.
Here.
What is this?
A stipend, there's gonna
be one every week.
$857 from Hamlin,
Hamlin, McGill?
I'm gonna pay them back,
every penny.
I didn't want
to take anything,
but Howard was very insistent.
And I'm gonna pay
you back, too.
Wait,
Hamlin was here?
It's not like
I'm a recluse.
What? He put his cellphone
in the mailbox?
He understands
the situation.
He grounded himself?
Of course.
And the two of you
agreed that since,
as everybody knows,
you're going back to work
any day now,
that the firm
should help you make
ends meet.
That's correct,
minus the sarcasm.
Hamlin's making you
a chump!
I'm going to get better!
I'm gonna
go back to work,
and I'm picking up
where I left off!
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(CLOCK TICKING)
Sorry.
Sorry, Chuck.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
I understand that you're
trying to look out for me,
but you're missing
the bigger picture.
I got it.
(SIGHS)
Speaking of which...
Howard brought this.
He's concerned.
JIMMY: What?
CHUCK: You have to admit,
it could be confusing,
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill?
James M McGill?
That's my name.
I was born with it. I...
Still...
How about Vanguard Law?
Or Gibraltar Legal...
Wait, wait.
So I'm not supposed
to use my name on,
and Hamlin's say-so?
(SCOFFS)
What's he gonna do, sue me?
Nobody wants to create
an adversarial situation.
I'm sure Howard
would gladly pay the cost
of new matchbooks
and so on.
(SIGHS) It's simply a matter
of professional courtesy.
(TICKING CONTINUES)
Chuck,
whose side are you on?
There are no sides.
But, Jimmy...
(SIGHS)
Wouldn't you rather
build your own identity?
Why ride on someone
else's coattails?
(SIGHING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
You want to dance, Howard?
(CHUCKLES) Let's dance.
MAN: With a backside on it.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Go!
No, you can get closer
than that, you bitch.
Come on.
And here it comes.
There you go. Better.
(CHEERING IN DISTANCE)
How was that?
It's right on here.
Take a look.
Still,
tighter is everything.
Tighter? What?
Tighter what?
I don't know.
Just stand tighter.
You know what I mean?
I don't know
what you mean.
LARS: That sucked.
We can call that
a stylistic choice, I guess,
if you want to...
Hey, fellas.
We got business.
How did you find us?
I know,
eerie, right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Come on.
Give me 30 seconds.
Could be the most profitable
30 seconds of your lives.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Let me tell you
about a young guy,
actually,
he's about your age.
He lived a long way from here
in a town called
Cicero, Illinois.
And in Cicero,
he was the man.
I mean, when he strolled
down the street,
all the corner boys
would give him
the high five.
All the finest babes
would smile at him
and hope
that he would smile back.
They called him
"Slippin' Jimmy,"
and everybody
wanted to be his friend.
"Slippin' Jimmy?"
What the hell kind of name
is that? (CHUCKLING)
Well,
I'll tell you, now,
winters in Cicero
are murder.
(CHUCKLES) You guys
growing up out here
in the golden west,
you don't know,
okay?
I'm talking cold
that'll freeze the snot
right in your nose.
I'm talking wind
that'll cut through
your jacket
and carve you up
like a Ginsu knife.
In fact,
most folks in Cicero
were scared of winter,
but not Jimmy.
Jimmy waited around
all summer,
and when September
finally rolled around
and he'd feel
that first cold wind
come sweeping off
lake Michigan,
he knew it was coming.
Was it Christmas?
Was it Kwanzaa?
Better, it was
slip 'n fall season.
Soon as it was
cold enough,
he'd find a nice,
smooth patch of ice.
State Street was good.
Michigan Avenue was better.
He'd pick his spot,
wait for it to get busy,
then he'd walk out
on the ice, and, boom!
He would biff it so hard,
people would come running
from five blocks away.
Yeah, but did he collect?
JIMMY: "Did he collect?"
Slippin' Jimmy
had it dialed in,
all right?
One good fall,
he'd clear 6, 8 grand.
That'd keep him
in old Milwaukee
and Maui Wowie
right through Labor Day.
8 grand?
8 grand.
Now, see,
I look at you guys,
I see potential.
The skateboard's
a nice wrinkle,
that makes it
a year-round gig.
And clearly, you know
how to take a header,
right?
But I got to ask you,
your best day ever,
how much
did you clear?
$630.
(SCOFFS)
630 bucks.
Was that
for one fall?
Two.
Two falls in one day.
(CHUCKLES)
Even at your age,
that's got to hurt.
True that.
All right, well,
I got a job for you.
How's 2 grand sound?
2 grand for one hit?
One hit.
Plus, you get to learn
from the best.
CAL: Nice boat.
JIMMY: Yeah, discreet, like
a stripper pole in a mosque.
Yeah, forget the boat.
Look at the car.
You know
what that is?
I don't know.
A station wagon?
It's a Mercury,
a 1988 Mercury Sable Wagon.
Remember it.
Burn it into your brains.
You got it?
It's a Mercury Sable Wagon,
sure.
JIMMY: Close your eyes.
What color is it?
Brown.
No, it's medium sandalwood.
Keep your eyes closed.
How does
the license plate start?
BOTH: Four.
Give those gentlemen
a gold star.
Betsy Kettleman's
her name.
Every weekday
between 2:25 and 2:50,
she comes through here
on her way to
pick up her kids
at Kit Carson Elementary.
Now, you need
a place where
she's gonna slow down,
am I right?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, there you go.
She slows down.
She hangs a right.
You come shooting out
of there.
You do what you did to me.
You go ass over teakettle.
You make it
a blue-ribbon special.
When she
gets out of the car,
you're sufferin'
St. Sebastian, right?
You're the hammer, okay?
You get in her face.
You scare the bejesus
out of her.
Give me your phone.
(SNIFFS)
It's kind of busy here,
don't you think?
(BEEPING)
Well, witnesses are good.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Witnesses are pressure,
all right?
Now, once you've got her
good and rattled,
then you call
for an ambulance,
but really,
you're calling for me.
I'm number one
on your speed dial,
right next
to your weed dealer.
You call me.
I hotfoot it over here.
I just happen
to be driving by.
I stop to see
what the trouble is,
and this is the
most important part,
you don't know me.
We've never met.
You got it?
Sure.
Okay.
Now, I'm Mrs. K's
White Knight.
We go  mano a mano.
You light into me, okay?
Get nasty. And no touching.
Leave the hair alone.
But otherwise,
you know, open season.
Yell. Stomp.
Call me a douche bag.
I'm gonna play it cool,
give you back
some of the razzmatazz.
And once she's seen
the fireworks,
you fold
like a lawn chair,
happy ending.
When do we get
our money?
After.
After?
You get paid
when I get paid.
I'm the rising tide
that raises all dinghies.
Now, pop quiz,
what's the car?
Mercury Sable Wagon.
Baby-poop brown.
Okay. Do you know me?
BOTH: No.
Damn straight.
Go with God.
JIMMY: Well, I'm just glad
I happened to be passing by.
Happy to be of help, Betsy.
May I call you "Betsy?"
(CLEARS THROAT)
Please, call me "James."
Hmm. Oh, the kid will be fine.
Don't worry.
He just got
his bell rung a little.
I'll, I'll handle that.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no.
I wouldn't think of, uh,
taking your money for this.
The embezzlement case?
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
Mm, yes, I'd,
I'd be happy to
talk it over.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, shit.
(SIGHS)
(DIALING)
Two-minute warning.
Got it.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Oh, my God!
MAN: What happened?
(CROWD MURMURING)
WOMAN: Call 911.
Oh, my God!
Cal! Cal!
Look at me!
Are you okay?
Buddy, say something.
Cal, what are you...
(GROANS)
Come on already.
What is she doing in there?
I don't know. Shh.
Is she making a sandwich?
Where's her sense
of responsibility?
(TIRES SQUEAL)
What?
Hey!
What the f...
Funny to run into you,
Betsy.
I was just, uh,
strolling the neighborhood.
You,
you were in accident.
Oh, it's...
(SIGHING)
Come on.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(CELLPHONE RINGS)
(BEEP)
Yeah?
LARS:  She took off on us.
She what?
It was textbook, man.
We were diamonds,
but then she just took off.
Okay, wait.
She, she hit-and-run?
That's what I'm saying.
She bailed and wailed.
Okay.
Just stay where you are.
I'll come get you.
No, no, no. Screw that, man.
(ENGINE SPUTTERS)
We're following her.
You're, how are,
you're following her how?
We got our ways, yo.
Okay, okay, okay, new plan,
new plan. You do know me.
I'm your lawyer.
You got that?
I'll meet you at the school.
No, she's way past
the school.
(ENGINE GRINDING)
She hooked a left
on Juan Tabo,
and she's coming
into Holiday Park.
Okay, stay with her.
When she gets
where she's going,
wherever that is,
just don't do anything.
Wait for me.
Wait for what?
You haven't been right
even once!
Slippin' Jimmy, my ass!
You fell into the honeypot,
kid.
You get it?
Hit-and-run is a felony.
So what?
(SCOFFS)
"So what?" so more money.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
He says we fell
in the honeypot.
He says "more money."
So what
do we need him for?
Cal? Lars?
Whoever, oh, damn it!
(DIALING)
(SIGHS) Come on. Come on!
(RINGING)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS)
LARS:  Do it. Do it. Do it.
Son of a bitch! (GRUNTS)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Come on!
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(SKATEBOARDS APPROACHING)
Hey. Hey, your leg.
Oh, I'm gonna do this one.
Okay. Hey!
Aah! Aah!
Hey, yo, hold up.
Hey, yeah, you,
what is the matter
with you?
You hit-and-run.
You ran him over.
You felonied my brother.
Que pasa?
Habla English.
We call,
we call  la policia.
La policia
gonna be pissed.
I see you hit him. Wham!
Aah.
You see that,
that windshield?
You did that.
No entiendo. No entiendo.
I did that.
You did that to me.
You did that. Now you pay.
No, senor. No, senor.
No entiendo.
Make, make with the  dinero.
Dinero?
Dinero.
Si, righteous  dinero.
Dinero?
Y,  si.
Okay.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about.
Talking about.
Mijo.
Let's go.
(GRUNTING)
Mijo!
CAL: Is that money?
Yeah.
Mijo...
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Watch this step.
CAL: Aah.
Watch this,
watch this step.
(CAL GRUNTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Where are you?
(SIGHS)
Holiday Park.
(SNIFFS)
Mrs. Kettleman, Betsy.
What are you doing here?
(SIGHS)
Hit-and-run?
That's very serious.
I can, I can mediate.
It's, I represent
their parents, so...
Come on. Come on.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(CAR DOOR CREAKS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SIGHS)
Open up!
Officer of the court!
Open up
in the name of the law!
(SNIFFS)
Good afternoon.
This...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CROW CAWS)
Movie1Dua.com